good morning it is Saturday
I forgot the month April 15 your 2020
otherwise known is the longest year in
existence knock on wood
we don't need 2021 to be longer so on
Saturday mornings I give an update on
what I have done that week and I'm gonna
try to start doing them in the form of
the five questions did you miss a
question because there used to be four
questions in oh there's a fifth question
which is part of the five questions this
week so I've had an eventful week which
I didn't even realize because it feels
very much like pre-pandemic it is
exactly pre-pandemic but I'm still
managing to move forward with what I'm
here to do and answering these five
questions and if I'm answering these
five questions well I've been the
pandemic I think I'm doing pretty good
so the five questions starting with Who
am I
it's like did I really learn Who I am
this week that I've learned anything
towards that it isn't every conversation
on part of and every day that I'm aware
in any way of learning things about
myself but actually yes this week I
signed up for this happiness course
through Coursera and part of what you do
in the first week is do a quiz on your
top traits your top no not on that you
also want to do it it's via character
org so BIA character org it's where you
take it and it's free and then they want
you to pay for it more information but I
got my top five strengths are creativity
fairness spirituality humor and
gratitude and yep that is definitely me
like it's and it's like in that order
and all the things that I can use to
actually put my creative ideas into
place or make the world more fair make
people able to answer these five
questions which is right now my
spirituality not make people invite
people to ask these five questions
empower them to answer them and anyway
it was like all the things to implement
it or down further it's like this is how
humanity comes together is that uneven
how many traits that are in total like
two
five-thirty that they rank for you and
it's like also ones to implement things
arrayed down but for other people those
ones are high and so it's about finding
the interconnectedness finding how we
bring out how we can concentrate on our
strengths and help each other overcome
our weaknesses because you don't need to
overcome them individually when someone
else can can actually do that piece of
it because who I'm supposed to be is
someone who is creative and fair and
spiritual and funny finds humor and
grateful and if I have to focus on being
the other things I'm gonna lose some of
that of what I'm here to do but that is
part of what I discovered about me this
week was these specific five topics I
also did coaching yesterday that's what
I do on Fridays is live coaching
sessions the last two weeks I've just
coached myself I tried this week also to
do a bit of like coaching the audience
helping them follow through with it
follow along with it and I focused on
relationship with others and the person
I have the most conflict in relationship
with others that I could always use help
processing is my sister and so that
brings us to our next question which are
who are my people and I love to meet
answering these five questions because
again I I didn't have it in that format
and then when I went to put it in this
format it was like oh I'm surrounded by
amazing people I had my idea cafe on
Tuesday where we talked about one of the
five questions two people showed up but
we had a conversation about who am i and
what that means to me and then I had the
Omega group that I'm part of on
Wednesdays two of them that earlier with
me to talk about four questions and we
came up with a fifth question during
that time period of like how can I help
create them in the world without being
the center and central leader I know I
want to be essentially I want most
things to be peer-to-peer I want it to
be as non hierarchical as it can be
without forcing it and that's pretty
easy because I'm not a higher person so
anything that I've been involved in is
by definition pretty non hierarchical
having me my COO and my people showed up
in on my Tuesday call who
they showed up for the Omega
conversation that we had to make amazing
conversation for the actual make a group
or the other two people came in and
joined and talking about yeah what we're
we're talk about gratitude and how it's
the someone who made us statements that
they wanted to talk about which was like
gratitudes the devil's work or something
along those lines and we were like no
but we would like talking about for two
hours we actually got we got a lot out
of it after all so having this
conversation about the four questions
where we generated a fifth question that
puts it even more in alignment with
these five quadrants that somebody else
came up with it's like how we save the
world which is I can't remember what
they are it's like code burden flow what
was about 100 um anyway I always mess up
his his for but so then the fourth
question is that everything the idea
together tech we had our together tech
meeting yesterday and really showed his
his project are his thing he's been
working on an AK which is a portal to
project so we can have in one place the
information for all of the projects that
together Tech is helping with whether
we've done a project raising for them
whether they show up to the roundtables
and those are starting to come together
to that more people are showing up
without interview force to those there's
one today there's the roundtable in 20
minutes I'm actually on attending it
because I have another conversation
Jordan put me in touch with somebody
who's involved in the Dow's stack and
I'm really looking forward to our
conversation this morning cuz something
he has an amazing project going on they
don't think we're gonna be able to use
it on in June a community based app a
social media app designed for community
and so I can't
I hope I'm hoping it's something new and
different and something that I'm
envisioning and not the same old same
old that's that's always been there but
whatever it's his project and his baby
and I'll be talking to him about what
that looks like and so those are my
people I'm surrounded by world-changing
thought leaders that in no way want to
be leaders these are these are my people
it's like the words leader know but like
actual embodiment of it yes just
everywhere and how those those people
come together to do things like create
the website that my brother created and
Bentley is working on his and we got to
see a bit of Jonas's I don't even know
what it's called
yonis is project hello many BAE and just
like people are making things and I am
holding solution raisins we had a
solution rising this week on which I
guess brings me to my purpose so what is
the third question so Who am I
I've figured out five of my top traits I
mean if it being them all but those the
top five that I wrote down and kept who
are my people just the world and even
went for a walk yesterday which we'll
get to also and I was like oh you only I
go out to be near people it's like no
you know you've never done that that's
not what you do I'm like I'm going out
to be away from people like no you
always went out for a lot to be in your
nature it's never really about the
people in fact if you could have found
it to yourself you probably would have
but anyway so my people and then oh and
then of course that's what else is here
just that I did release that emotional
charge around my relationship with my
sister I'm almost ready to get back in
contact with her tomorrow Sunday morning
is story time so I'm doing the story
time on my sister and our relationship
our life so far and then I'm going to
reach out to her as to you to put the
ball in her court kind of up saying I'm
ready to have a conversation let me know
when you are and setting that up which
is actually by the deadline even though
I was part of what I got out of the
coaching and was like you can't do this
on a deadline just go mid-nineteen just
because my nephews about to turn one I
can't actually have this arbitrary
deadline but I can put the ball in her
court and sleeve it up to the universe
and I think I'm 90% of the way there and
that is the diminishing returns like I'm
never going to get a hundred percent
away there's my purpose my purpose what
is my purpose my purpose is to create a
world that works for everyone and to
follow my next GPS coordinate to follow
just the next thing that I'm supposed to
do because if I'm like I have to save
the world it's way too much for anyone
clearly but doing the next thing
surrendering to what I'm here to do is
much easier especially since it's like
just the next thing that I have to do
and all honesty I did a lot this week
I did all of my normal stuff like I had
the idea Cafe which we did on Who am I I
which was amazing because it was on the
five questions we held that conversation
came up with a fifth question which
we're gonna get to did the together tech
thing yesterday as I said that's coming
together we did the solution race and
stay and that was interesting and and
fun and we did it on fragility and
efficiency you want me to show this
right now I was okay part of also my
kids purpose is being an artist and she
made this and really wanted me to show
it to the world she wanted the world to
see it there's a tree kind of see here
quite there's like a little bush with
leaves that she's made and this is a cat
she is she said she's yet to figure out
how to make a cat in this particular
medium but it is this she draws amazing
cats so by purpose but that that is for
my purpose being a parent and having to
figure out how to like homeschool and
figuring out that dynamic of not being
able to leave it up to the school system
to have my kids learn to read and do
basic math like okay this is a little
bit more on me now with our unique
situation that hurt old school close the
end last year she had this school but it
was believed anyway it's quite fun time
so I did the solution raising we did
together tech meeting yesterday when we
found heard about the new ideas I had
the idea cafe on Who am I plus one I
love what I can't read my writing oh and
I did the so Nick had mentioned doing
a document something that says
everything I'm up to because I'm a
little hard to keep track of I'm not
like three different YouTube channels
none of which have this one has the most
subscribers 150 it's like the together
tech the idea cafe anyway so I'm writing
a document that I can then post in all
of my videos of like here's what I'm up
to here's what all the projects are them
up to you a little bit of a glossary and
a little bit of like here's what
together tech is here's one idea cafe is
and so I'm almost done that I was
working on this morning
and now we get to the fourth quest
which is what do I need and realizing
yesterday when I went for my second walk
since the Pens haven't started I was
like oh my god why aren't I doing this
every day
I need to one of the people in game B
had done a meditation challenge that was
like yeah I'll do that
identity I've meditated once he's on
like day 25 although I do
meditate when it's my Coleen like when
it comes from me and I'm like I'm gonna
meditate for the next 30 days
then it happens it's wonderful
no you're talking about Shila missing
parts so and that reminds me
Shiloh we had a conversation this week
and that was amazing and in shyla is
definitely one of my people probably
been more than some others right like we
have very similar purpose on this planet
and that feels amazing to have somebody
else to to relate to who who has a
Colleen it feels like they're here to
also help save the world
it's like the weirdness that's
associated with that and not be able to
get it out in the world and like owning
it but not like I understand what the
Fabri dick Ulysses sounds like I know
how to save the world and stay tuned
stay tuned it's gonna happen profess
purpose purpose no bronze needs so I
realized that one of the things I need
my family to get to the world needs is
for me to go for this walk every day
every day that's somewhat nice out o
your daughters are patient thank you she
was like what are we talking about
yes she is she's an artist which is also
part of like how perfect it is that she
is my daughter because I would I tell
her this all this like I wouldn't have
thought to pick an artist as a child if
I had a checkbox to like but I got one
right I got an artist Kylie was saying
that she likes your art your art is
wonderful this is my art I made the
artist does that count
anyway I'm flexible too you are you're a
ballerina and an artist yeah I am
neither of those things although I am
flexible in a weird way because of how I
sit constantly but not an idiot Thank
You Nana splits you can you can do
splits
and you even tried you couldn't quite do
them and then you tried harder and
harder to do them and you like you
taught your body to do them is a couple
weeks until you can do it completely
yeah okay can you give me like five more
minutes to do this all right how about
Saturday she would have been home anyway
I just wouldn't necessarily been doing
these on Saturday without it so purpose
my that I'm going to be going out to the
to the world and going for a nature walk
every day because it's again what I need
my family needs the world needs I'm like
yes the going yesterday was just so
amazing I basically just walk around
singing to myself in nature and I'm
gonna go
I've also one of the things that I don't
know which category fits in but I've
been a child I'm never coming or singing
to yourself if you're embarrassed by
that I never wanna hang out with you
done all I do is walk around and think
to myself it's helpful generate
something fully I could if I could
explain my Indian song but this all the
lyrics make me no sense to anyone but me
so it's like alright this is not me
singing about the possibility of the
world is not gonna help in any way nor
are they talking about the other tech
and I was solutions cooperative can help
us but have you know nature knowing
that's what I need in the fifth question
the one that the people help me come up
with it is very tie-in to Lawrence's
four and the fifth part which is burn is
what am I ready to let go of what's
ready to be let go of and with the Who
am I who are my people what is my
purpose and what do I need it's also
like what do I need what can I let go of
and so I've let go of some of the
emotion with my sister but the life
coach she needing it to look a certain
way a little bit though the world needs
to look a certain way accept
really did hit me yesterday when I was
up for my walk how ironic it is that
this pandemic it's pretty peaceful for
me for the world in the West yet it's
still hard and knowing what this looks
like
maybe possibly if Mother Nature is this
neutral meeting I'm neutral anyway well
this is gonna look like in Africa and
India and country in war-torn countries
ones that are currently you know have no
infrastructure what this looks like in
refugee camps and knowing that and like
the heaviness of about hitting me and
like well I can't I can't take that on
that can't be mine how do I use that as
fuel to actually move me forward without
it paralyzing me and making me not be
able to do anything and I think it's
just constantly owning that that I'm
lucky to be going through this as easily
as as we are and if we can use any
amount of that energy that time we freed
up to help help people in the rest of
the world cuz I don't want to live
through a pandemic and a famine and
things that we're not going to be able
to help with so I can't do it all but I
can I can do my piece which is five
questions and the solution raising and
anything that I can actually do that's
the next GPS step and so tomorrow I'm
gonna be on sharing the story with my
sister seeking about before I can
release like the final so it's
explaining yesterday that I haven't I
haven't I told the story a lot when it
first happened around this time last
year I was rather obsessed with it and
I've done a lot over the last year to
kind of let it go to work on my
emotional charge around it but Anna most
of the way there I'm almost back to
neutral with her in an emotional state
so we'll see we'll see telling the story
whether that's still the case whether I
can tell the story and beam on emotional
state how much that story I'm telling in
whatever it's gonna be tomorrow and then
following these five questions or word
they're on it's weird cuz they're at
their own project but yet they're not a
project like the five questions are just
ongoing project I'm gonna redo my video
on my youtube channel
the Jubilee saves the world by
meandering through life to categor those
5 questions to say like that's of what
the channel is is me working through my
five questions that's what these updates
on Saturday are going to be is actually
me forming a formulating it in those
five questions what have I learned about
myself how how have the universe showed
me who my people are how have i stepped
forward in any way with my purpose what
do I need to be able to do any of that
including in my own life ie they going
for a walk every day and also what I've
done which I keep trying to mention not
mention is that um I've been reducing my
marijuana intake knowing that I am in no
way capable right now of cutting it out
like sometimes I do I'll cut it out for
two weeks and that does not feel
conducive to what I'm capable of the
moment but I am capable of last week it
was not doing it saloon and now it's not
doing it to 1 p.m. and as of Monday not
doing it to 2 p.m. and I might stay with
you p.m. for a while yeah I left that
question - it wasn't even my question it
was like to do with the burn it was like
what are we to let go of and and it's
willing to it's not like it's not a
force because that to me as always like
someone else telling me that I have to
like let go of my diet like something
let go not exercise like oh and like
that's not yours to say it's like what
are you willing to let go and that's
about these 5 questions is and stay on
the game be space like the with Jordan
and John for baekje of the religion
that's not a religion and there does
need to be something that ties us
together how loosely and yet tightly
that is tied together is going to impact
a lot right we can't wait
there is no village and everyone thinks
for everyone there's nothing that ties
us together but if it's like we have to
follow the tenets of this book that was
written 2,000 years ago then it's harder
to like then it's the book that's tying
you together not actually your choice to
be there and like what if someone is not
following the road the bike renee still
there to me answering these five
questions is the path to happiness the
path to purpose and the more anyone
answers them it already is its own
reward it's like well me answer though
helps me
no one else has to force me to do it
because in answering them I get the
internal reward of knowing myself more
being connected to people walking my
purpose which like there's nothing
outside of you once you start doing that
path and that process there's nothing
outside of you they can take it away
like they're like no one can be like
well give you a million dollars if you
just stop I'm certain these questions no
not happening
and yes I like so I've been on for 20
minutes
I'm actually not attending the thing in
ten minutes because I have another
conversation in an hour and a bit with
the guy Jordan put me in touch with the
Dallas tax so I am which we will see if
we're recording it we're gonna decide at
the moment and it may be available on
this YouTube channel or not
might be private on this YouTube channel
might not be recorded I'm leaving it up
to chance usually okay with them breathe
that like we'll just show up look at
their go live or we won't on private
mode um it's not just what I've been up
to same old thing happening this coming
week I will be doing a Tuesday idea cafe
this week I believe it will be like who
are my people because we're gonna ever
answering the five questions over the
next five weeks just to see what that
looks like in an ID a cafe and exploring
the five I'm sitting with the five
questions like how can I help people
start on this path how can we help each
other on this path without there being a
central leader right like I I haven't
answered these questions and now I'm
gonna like delve into exactly how you
answer who you are it's an ongoing
process I don't know necessarily how to
help people find their purpose I kind of
do it's like it's there's Clues all
throughout your life what's easy for you
that's hard for everybody else and
what's hard for you that's easy for
everybody else that's your key those
state things tied together yes fine you
know you don't even know it's easy for
you it's hard for other people cuz it's
so easy for you assume it's easy for
everybody else and then you usually know
what's hard for you but you like are
down on yourself about it it's like
right well someone had to have that be
hard for them it's you welcome to your
purpose and helping people find their
their people I think we can create tools
for that rather simply but the universe
to you no matter what the people in your
life are your people the good ones the
bad ones all of them they're here to
show you who you are and they're here to
show up in amazing way it's like my
people this week I until I sat down to
did this I was like I'm so alone in my
house like no I'm not the universe get
you I know I'm a little alone because I
haven't reached out like my actual real
world community friends and family cuz
everyone else is doing that I'm like I
don't have the spoons I'm trying to save
the world and raise the kids it's not
going to school and owning that bit like
right I actually have less capacity than
I thought I would during this quarantine
due to the fact that oh right I have a
disability that's why I'm home everyone
else stayed at home doesn't have that
disability and that shows up in a real
way so that is what I've done this last
week that's what I'm doing this coming
week did I go through Tuesday right idea
cafe Wednesday we're doing the solution
raising here on this channel on
packaging and materials and then Friday
I'll be doing coaching on relationship
with self as opposed to we just did
relationship with others and I will be
scanning okay this last time I was like
holding up the list and try to read them
and do them myself
well show me them as everyone else so
I'm going to instead scan the things
that I need and have the link to that
scanning the folder those are scanned in
in the description of the YouTube video
for Friday and then next Friday and next
Saturday of course with together tech
we're doing our board meeting and our
roundtable usual roundtable on Saturday
mornings which I'm really enjoying
because more and more people are coming
in and that is I'm up to just meandering
through life saving the world just same
old same old alright I will see you all
tomorrow for storytime hopeful see how
that works I might go for my walk
earlier than 8:30 tomorrow so that I can
connect with nature nature reminds me
that everything's happens in exactly the
right way including my drama with my
sister especially my drama with my
sister which is why one share the story
is because it's it's a huge it ties in
with everything in life and also was
things it was not in any way what I
asked to happen and exactly what
to happen including this year apart so I
will be sharing that story tomorrow and
I will see you then take care thanks for
hanging up